你们有听说过有个研究小组
Have you guys heard about this research team
想要从基因方面操控鸡的DNA
that's trying to genetically manipulate Chicken DNA
来创造某种类似鸡恐龙的事情吗
to create some sort of a chicken dinosaur?
我觉得这听起来超赞啊
I think that sounds wonderful.
什么  你不是又怕恐龙又怕鸡吗
What? You're afraid of both dinosaurs and chickens.
是啊  但你敢说
Yes, but tell me
鸡恐龙肉沙拉三明治
a dinosaur chicken salad sandwich
不会正中美味白垩纪之点吗
wouldn't hit the Mesozoic spot.
-你们好啊  -你好
- Hey, guys. - Hey. Hello.
明晚都会出席的吧
We still on for tomorrow night?
当然  我很期待终于能见到你的女朋友呢
Yeah. I'm excited to finally meet your girlfriend.
是啊  说到这事
Yeah, oh, and speaking of which.
根据牛津大学最新的研究指出
According to a recent study out of Oxford University,
一个人有了新的浪漫伴侣之后
when someone takes on a new romantic partner,
会失去一到两个好朋友
that person loses one or two close friends.
你什么时候开始看社会科学了
Since when do you read social science?
我也会上厕所  也需要厕所读物啊
I go to the bathroom like everybody else.
为什么我会因为有了对象而失去朋友呢
Why would I lose friends just because I started dating someone?
是啊  你跟艾米好上后  也没少了朋友啊
Yeah, you didn't lose anyone when you met Amy.
人家研究是说浪漫伴侣
Yeah, well, no, the study refers to romantic partners.
我可不会把我们的关系归到这一类
Not the way I would categorize the two of us.
你们也接吻和牵手啊
You guys kiss and hold hands.
我看过他们做这些事  完全不浪漫
I've seen him do it. It's not romantic.
我可不是那种
Look, I'm not the kind of guy
一谈恋爱就会重色轻友的人
who drops his friends just because he's in a relationship.
要是她不喜欢我们呢
What happens if she doesn't like us?
别这样  你们可是我的好朋友
Well, hey, you're my dear friends.
开始几年  我还是会给你们寄圣诞卡
You'll get a Christmas card for a couple of years,
之后你们哪凉快死哪去
and then you're dead to me.
霍华德  斯图尔特还跟你妈住在一起吗
So, Howard, is Stuart still living with your mom?
我不想谈这事
I don't want to talk about it.
-但他还是会谈  -我妈帮他装了收费台
- But he's going to. - My mom got him cable!
我从小到大
In my whole life,
住在那个房子里  就没看过收费台
growing up in that house-- no cable.
你知道我妈付钱
Do you know how many HBOs
给那寄生虫装了多少电影频道吗  七个
that leech had my mother get him? Seven.
七个电影频道呢  七个啊
Seven HBOs. Seven!
长话短说  就是他们有七个电影频道
Long story short, they have seven HBOs.
各位
Hey, guys.
你好
Hello.
-艾米丽  在座各位你差不多都认识  -你好
- Emily, you know almost everybody here. - Hi.
这位是莱纳德  这是佩妮
This is Leonard, this is Penny.
幸会幸会
Oh, it's so nice to meet you.
-我也是  -你好
- Nice to finally meet you, too. - Hi.
好
Hello.
拉杰  你真的没骗我们
Well, Raj, you were not lying about her.
我就说她真实存在
I told you she exists.
我听说你是皮肤科医生
Hey, I hear you're a dermatologist.
是的  我是亨廷顿医院的住院医师
Uh, yeah, I'm a resident at Huntington Hospital.
我好喜欢他们的急诊室
Oh, I like their emergency room.
就算检查结果显示你没得登革热
Yeah, even if it turns out you don't have Dengue fever,
你还是可以拿根棒棒糖
they still let you take a lollipop.
佩妮刚刚开始
You know, Penny just started training
医药销售的培训
to be a pharmaceutical sales rep.
或许有机会她可以跟你练习练习
Maybe she can practice on you some time.
如果能跟一名真医生练习就太好了
Oh, it would be great to practice on a real doctor.
可以啊  没问题
Yeah. I'm sure that'd be fine.
我的屁屁上有些奇怪的斑点
I have some odd freckles on my buttocks.
我能跟你约个时间就诊吗
Can I make an appointment for you to look at them?
应该...  可以吧
Um... okay, I guess.
我都跟了他三年  毛都没捞着
I'm with him three years, nothing.
她刚进来两分钟  他就要对人脱裤子了
She's with two minutes, and he's taking his pants off.
昨晚挺有意思  你觉得艾米丽如何
Last night was fun. What did you think of Emily?
不知道
I don't know.
我感觉她好像不太喜欢我
I kind of got the sense she didn't like me.
她有说她不喜欢你吗
Did she say she didn't like you?
当然没有  才不会有人
Of course not. No one ever says
当着你的面说不喜欢你呢
they don't like you straight to your face.
咱俩的人生路真是大不同啊
We have led different lives.
你们才刚认识  你怎么会有这种感觉呢
You guys just met. Why would she feel that way?
我就是感觉到了
It's just this vibe I got.
应该是你想太多了
I'm sure you're worried about nothing.
我想你说得对
Yeah. You're probably right.
我曾经以为我高中的体育老师不喜欢我
I used to think my high school P.E. Teacher didn't like me,
后来发现  她是"太"喜欢我
but it turned out, she liked me a little too much.
-真的吗  -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
也还好啦
It was fine.
我们一起去了梅莉莎·埃瑟里奇的演唱会
We went to a Melissa Etheridge concert,
梅莉莎·埃瑟里奇  美国女歌手
也是积极参与同志权利运动的社会活动家
我后来成绩得了A  一切圆满
I got an A, it all worked out.
等你去她办公室练习  你就知道你多虑了
When you go to Emily's office to practice, you'll see. It's fine.
希望就像你说的吧
Yeah, I hope you're right.
你真的这辈子从未试过
You really went your entire life
有人当面对你说"我讨厌你"吗
without anyone saying "I hate you" to your face?
对啊
Yeah.
我现在就想对你说  但瞧你那迷人的颧骨
I'd say it now, but look at those cheekbones.
我好想念斯图尔特的店
I miss Stuart's place.
看这店吵杂的音乐  露出的砖墙
All this loud music and exposed brick.
这里是漫画书店
What, is this a comic book store,
还是第三只小猪砖房家中的派对啊
or a rave at the third little pig's house?
是啊  我也希望斯图尔特重新开店
Yup, I wish Stuart would reopen.
我也讨厌这家店
I hate this place, too.
我相信他是真心的
Okay, him I believe
因为他就是个80岁老头穿15岁小孩的衣服
because he's an 80-year-old man in a 15-year-old's T-shirt.
但你只是在不爽
But you're just upset about
斯图尔特和你妈以及他们的付费电影台
Stuart and your mom and all their HBOs.
没错
Yes, I am.
我现在看《权力的游戏》时  都会想到
You know, I can't even watch Game of Thrones now
我妈在问他
without thinking of mother saying,
"斯图尔特  他们谁是'权力'"
"Stuart, which one is Thrones?"
他可能不能重新开张
You know, he might not reopen.
保险公司没赔给他多少钱
He didn't get a lot of money from the insurance company.
天啊  如果有一件事能让我生气
Oh, boy, if there is one thing that gets my goat,
就是那些该死的保险公司
it's those dad-gum insurance companies.
为什么  因为他们整天来烦你这死老头吗
Why? Because they won't get off your lawn?
斯尔图特有试着去贷款  或找人投资吗
Oh, is Stuart trying to get a loan, or-or find investors?
我只知道他让我妈
All I know is, he's got my mother
给他买四层的厕纸
buying four-ply toilet paper.
四层的啊
I mean, four-ply.
如果他的屁股那么娇气
If his butt is so delicate,
干嘛不直接用安哥拉兔子擦呢
why doesn't he just use an angora rabbit?
安哥拉兔毛颜色洁白  轻细  滑软  美观  暖和
是一种高级纺织原料
首先它们会掉毛  还会咬人
For starters, they shed and bite.
我有个想法
Hey, here's a thought.
我们何不帮斯尔图特把剩下的钱凑够呢
Why don't we put up the rest of the money that Stuart needs?
那我们就是漫画书店的店主了
So, we'd be, like, owners of a comic book store?
就像是美梦成真
It's kind of a dream come true.
听起来蛮有意思
That does sound fun.
或许我们还能想出
Ooh, maybe we could come up
一个跟这地方抗衡的商业计划
with a business plan to compete with this place.
我现在就有一个计划
I'll give you a plan right now.
第一步  开一家漫画书店
Step one: open comic book store.
第二步  散布谣言
Step two: start rumor
说这家漫画书店会让人得生殖器疣
this comic book store gives you genital warts.
第三步  买一个大袋子装钱
Step three: buy a big bag to put the money in.
这计划还不错
It's not that bad.
非常感谢你能当我的客户  让我练习推销说辞
Thank you so much for letting me practice my sales pitch on you.
我真的感激不尽
I really appreciate it.
-没事  -我给你买了咖啡
- Sure. - Um, I brought coffee.
我不太确定你喜欢哪种  所以我买了
I wasn't sure what you like, so I got
普通咖啡  卡布奇诺和印度拉茶各一杯
a regular, a cappuccino and a Chai tea.
因为你喜欢拉杰  所以我想你可能喜欢印度口味
Since you like Raj, I thought you might be into that.
谢谢  我们开始吧  我有点忙
Thanks. If we could get started. I'm a little busy.
当然可以  让我先把材料拿出来
Oh, yeah, sure. Let me just get out my materials.
这手提包是莱纳德给我的
Leonard gave me this briefcase.
他高中时随身带着它
He used to carry it around in high school.
所以老被人拿来打他  现在还能看见凹痕呢
You can still see the dent where they whacked him with it.
进入正题  我想介绍一下
Okay, I would like to talk to you
我们新出的避孕药  弗米拉
about our new birth control pill, Femevra.
好的
Great.
弗米拉三相口服避孕药
So, Femevra's triphasic design
每一周期仿造正常月经周期中荷尔蒙的变化
含有三种不同比例的雌激素与黄体素
能平衡荷尔蒙
provides balanced hormonal exposure.
好的
All right.
同时还有实验表明
It has also been shown to cause
它相比其他口服避孕药  副作用少了很多
significantly fewer side effects than other oral contraceptives.
尽管它会导致长青春痘  但是我个人意见
Although it can cause acne, which, if you ask me, kind of
这也能增加"避孕"的有效性  不是吗
increases its effectiveness as a contraceptive.
呵呵
Funny.
抱歉  我一开始就给了你不好的印象吗
Okay, I'm sorry. Did we get off on the wrong foot?
因为从那晚开始  我就隐约感觉到
Because since the other night, I kind of feel like
你可能对我有意见
you might have a problem with me.
不  没有啊
No, it's fine.
你确定吗  因为看起来不像没有
Are you sure, because it doesn't seem fine?
好吧
Okay.
如果你真的想谈论此事
If you really want to talk about this,
我的确对你有意见
I do have a problem.
天啊  告诉我  我做错了什么
Oh, my God. Tell me-- what did I do?
其实没什么  只是...
Look, it's nothing. It's just...
拉杰告诉我  不久之前你们有过一段
Raj told me that a while ago, you two hooked up.
什么  他为什么要说
What?! Oh, why would he say that?
那没有吗
Did it not happen?
确切来说  那不能称为"有过一段"
Well, I wouldn't exactly call it a hook-up.
你们接吻了吗
Did you kiss?
接了
Yeah.
你们俩脱光光了吗
Were you naked?
脱了
Yeah.
那就是啊
So, it was a hook-up.
不是
No.
算是吧
Yeah.
有什么办法能让我们的漫画书店
So, what are some ways we could set our comic book store
在同行中脱颖而出
apart from the competition?
买漫画的都是小孩  如果能有办法
Oh, kids buy comic books. It would be great
让更多的小孩来我们店  那就最好了
to figure out a way to get more kids in the store.
在我小的时候  我喜欢去漫画书店
You know, when I was a kid, I loved going there,
但没人载我去
but I could never get a ride.
如果我们搞个面包车
Ooh, what if we got a van
专门在大街上接小孩呢
and drove around and picked kids up?
好主意
Nice.
你是说去公园和学校守着吗
You mean, like at parks and schools?
还有玩具店  木偶剧院
Toy stores, puppet shows.
等等  你们的主意是搞个面包车
Hold on. So, your idea is to get a van
在大街上兜来兜去  专门接小孩吗
and cruise the streets looking for kids to pick up?
是的
Yes.
你们要用糖果引诱他们上车吗[绑架]
And are you gonna use candy to lure them in?
这个主意好
We are now!
你告诉艾米丽我们有过一段吗
You told Emily we hooked up?!
我要辩一句  我告诉了所有人
Um, well, in my defense, I tell everybody.
你为什么要那样说
Why would you say that?!
我们当时在聊过去的爱人
We were having a conversation about past lovers.
我们不是爱人  拜托
We weren't lovers! Come on.
大家都知道我们没有上床
Everyone knows we didn't sleep together.
我们只是喝醉了鬼混而已
We got drunk and fooled around.
你们聊的时候就不能不说到我吗
Why couldn't you just leave me out of it?
我们说了要对彼此坦诚
Well, we were being honest.
那如果你甩了莱纳德后
You would leave me out of the conversation
你和下一个男人聊这话题时  不会说到他吗
with the next guy if you dump Leonard?
-干嘛扯到我  -不会
- Why say it? - Yes!
我决不会把你从我的名单除名
Well, I would never leave you off my list,
而且不是因为不提你
and not just because, without you,
"名单"可能就不太够数了哦
we're playing fast and loose with the word "list."
干得好  现在她讨厌我了
Well, good job. Now she hates me.
棒极了
Great.
往好的方面看  牛津大学的研究是对的
On the bright side, that Oxford study was right.
朋友减一了
One friend down.
我好奇下一个会是谁呢
I wonder who you're going to lose next.
你  就是你  下一个就是你
You, okay? It's you. You're-you're next!
才怪  你这么喜欢我
No. You're crazy about me.
我不懂艾米丽干嘛这么生气
I don't know what Emily's so upset about anyway.
就算我俩睡过了  那又怎样
Even if I had slept with him, so what?
每个人都有过去
Everyone has a past.
几乎每个人都有过去
Almost everyone has a past.
拜托  你这么漂亮
Come on, look how pretty you are.
她肯定不是第一个讨厌你的女生
I'm sure this isn't the first girl to hate you.
的确不是
It's not.
你肯定能改变她的想法
And I'm sure you can turn it around.
怎么改  总不能逼着别人喜欢你吧
How? You can't force someone to like you.
不如你多和她相处  装出闺蜜的样子
What if you just hang around and act like her friend
逐渐让她喜欢上你
until you wear her down?
接下来  你就登堂入室
I mean, next thing you know, you're in her home,
吃着她家的零食  喝着她家的美酒
you're eating her food, drinking her wine.
这招不管用
No, that won't work.
说得对  干杯
You're right. Cheers.
我知道了
Oh, I know.
干嘛不利用你的销售技巧
Why don't you use your sales training
好好向她推销一番你自己呢
to go back down there and sell yourself?
-什么  -真的
- What? - Yeah.
不是去推销药物
But instead of selling a drug,
而是去推销佩妮  多可爱啊
you'd be selling Penny-- it's cute.
多傻逼啊
It's stupid.
要是你不这么鄙视来否定别人的建议
Well, maybe people would like you more
大家也许会更喜欢你
if you didn't crap all over their ideas.
这一点我同意佩妮的看法
I'm gonna go with Penny on this one.
这也是理所当然的  我们可是老朋友了
Then again, why wouldn't I? I mean, we go way back.
对哦  我以前不喜欢你呢
Oh, my God. I didn't used to like you.
别说  艾米在这会听到
Shh. Amy's here now.
我越考虑开店这事
You know, the more I think about it,
就越觉得有兴趣
the more intrigued I am about having our own store.
新书还没上架
We'll get to see all the new stuff
我们早就看过了
before it hits the shelves.
我们还能和顾客们友好互动
And we'll get to have fun interactions with our customers.
"这里不是图书馆  不买就滚"
"This isn't a library-- buy it or get out."
你不是整天对人这么说吗
You say things like that all the time.
是啊  可我要是店主
Yes, but as a store owner,
别人说"店又不是你开的  闭嘴"时
I'll finally have a good comeback to,
我就能理直气壮顶回去了
"You don't work here-- shut up."
你记得佩妮对拉杰说
Uh, do you know how Penny told Raj he should have
-把她从名单上划掉吗  -记得
- left her off his list? - Yeah.
那你觉得我跟她聊这事时
Well, do you think when she and I had that conversation,
她是不是也划掉了某些人呢
she left people off her list?
肯定啊
I'm sure she did.
为什么
Why?
如果她一个都没省略
Because if she hadn't,
那名单现在还没念完呢
she'd still be wading through the list.
你能不能别凑进来
Will you stay out of this?
这句话应该是佩妮的台词吧
If only Penny had said that once in a while.
那又有什么关系呢
Hey, what difference does it make?
你才是她想嫁的那个人
You're the one she wants to marry.
说得对
That's true.
而且我觉得恋人之间的绝对坦诚
Yeah, and I'm not sure that complete honesty
不一定是件好事
is always the best thing for a relationship.
他说得对
Yeah, he's right.
有一次我向艾米坦白
Once, in a moment of candor,
说她的头发让我想起了
I told Amy that her hair reminded me
沾满泄漏的石油的海鸭  结果...
of a duck caught in an oil spill. Well...
她气得夺门而出
she stormed out.
实在可悲  因为我们正在玩拼字游戏
Which was sad, because we were playing Scrabble,
我马上就要拼出"美洲柿"这词了
and I had all the letters to spell "persimmon."
你跟我们瞎凑什么热闹啊
Why are you even part of this conversation?
你根本就不懂女人
You don't know anything about women.
我知道如果我有老婆或未婚妻
I know that if I had a wife or a fiance,
那我投资漫画书店之前
I'd ask her first before I invested money
肯定先问问她的意见
in a comic book store.
他说得对
He's right.
我当然说得对
Yeah, well, of course I am.
我对她头发的评价也是对的
I was also right about her hair.
跟鸭子完全一样  除了不嘎嘎叫
It did everything but quack.
有件事我想告诉你一下
There's something I wanted to run past you.
什么事
What's up?
我和小伙伴们准备
Mm, the guys and I were thinking about
投资斯图尔特的漫画书店
investing in Stuart's comic book store.
-你觉得好吗  -干嘛问我
- Is that okay? - Why are you asking me?
我们订婚了
Well, you know, we're engaged,
这可是重大的财务问题
and it's kind of a big deal financially.
我想我俩应该讨论一下
It seems like something we should talk about.
那你觉得身负大笔信用卡债务
Well, would you consider mounds of credit card debt
算不算重大的财务问题呢
kind of a big deal financially?
算
Yeah.
我和小伙伴们在讨论
So, me and the guys were talking about
这个绝佳的投资机会
this great investment opportunity...
不行
Nope.
你都不知道是什么呢
But you didn't hear what it was.
我能猜到
I know.
别这样嘛
Oh, come on.
好吧  是什么
Fine. What is it?
我们想帮忙重开漫画书店
It's to help reopen the comic book store.
不行
Nope.
听我说完嘛
Well, hear me out.
霍华德  你知道我们在存钱买房子
Howard, you know we're saving up for a house.
我知道  可大家都会入伙
I know, but all the guys are doing it.
一人只需出四分之一
We're splitting it four ways,
所以不会花太多钱
so it's really not that much money.
这投资感觉风险挺大
It just seems like a risky investment.
我明白
I get that. I...
听我说
Okay, look...
我非常想开店的原因是
The reason this is important is...
在我爸抛弃我和妈妈之前
...before my dad left me and my mom...
他经常带我去漫画店
he used to... take me to the comic book store.
这是我们拥有过为数不多的父子时光
It was one of the few things we did together.
华仔  我不知道这件事
Oh. Howie, I had no idea.
我也...不爱对人提这件事
Well, I don't... like to talk about it.
亲爱的
Oh, baby.
这事是你瞎掰的  对吗
That story's made up, isn't it?
为了买下漫画店  我豁出去了
That's how much buying a comic book store means to me.
我希望你能诚实地给我一些意见
I'd like your honest opinion on something.
没问题
Of course.
在我提问前
Now, before I start,
你要知道  我对此事非常激动
I need you to know that I'm very excited about this,
所以你所说的每一句话
and anything you say
如果不够掏心掏肺百分百支持
that isn't enthusiastically supportive
将会令我们的感情产生问题
will throw our entire relationship into question.
所以
So...
保持开放的心态
keep an open mind.
我感觉无路可走唯有附和了  谢尔顿
I'm feeling a little backed into a corner, Sheldon.
这就对了  现在
Perfect. Now...
我在考虑投资
...I'm considering investing
斯图尔特的漫画店
in Stuart's comic book store.
有意思
Interesting.
你不觉得一个成年男子
Can you see how a grown man,
而且是颇有成就的科学家
an accomplished scientist,
投资一家
who invests in a store
出售图画书
that sells picture books
主角是穿着色彩斑斓内裤的飞人们
about flying men in colorful underwear...
也许是浪费他的财务
...might be wasting both his financial
和智力资源吗
and intellectual resources?
不觉得
No.
那我觉得这个想法太棒了
Then I think it's a terrific idea.
很好
Great.
我们面包车的想法更棒哦
Wait till you hear about our van.
谢谢你邀请我们过来
Thanks for inviting us over.
感谢你们能来
Oh, thank you for coming.
佩妮  你开始之前
Uh, listen, Penny, before you start,
我要先道歉  我那天在办公室
I just want to apologize for being so rude
太没礼貌了
the other day in my office.
不  不需要道歉
No, no. No need to apologize.
打扰下  我能说些什么吗
Excuse me, can I say something?
我爱你们两个
I just love both you guys,
我希望你们合得来
and I want you to get along.
我说的"爱"  对你是朋友之爱
And when I say "love," I meant as a friend.
咱俩之间说"爱"太快了  对吗
And, uh, way too soon, right?
坐下吧  听我说  艾米莉
Okay, sit down. Listen, Emily,
我和拉杰的事
what happened between me and Raj
-已经是陈年旧事了  -没错
- was a long time ago. - It was,
而且我也不该在这件事上小题大作
and I may have made it seem like a bigger deal than I should have.
现在莱纳德和我订婚了
Yeah, and Leonard and I are engaged now,
我希望这事大家就既往不咎吧
and I'm just hoping we can put this whole thing behind us.
我也希望这样
I'd like that, too.
我本来以为我不会心里不舒服
Yeah, I thought I'd be okay with it,
但结果看到你这么漂亮
but then I saw how pretty you are.
你嘴真甜
Oh, that's so sweet.
瞧你  这么美
I mean, look at you-- you are gorgeous.
没错  你俩都美呆了
It's true-- you're both gorgeous.
把这两朵娇花带上床的男人该有多优秀啊
Kind of says something about the man who could bed you both.
你明白为啥我大半辈子都孤单一人了吧
You get why I've been alone most of my adult life.
什么风把你们吹来了
So, what brings you by?
我来这里不需要原因  这是我的房子
Well, I don't need a reason-- it's my house.
确切来说  这是你妈妈的房子  但是
Technically, it's your mom's house, but...
我们还是希望你能觉得自己是受欢迎的
we certainly want you to feel welcome.
我永远都受欢迎
I'm always welcome.
只是  下次来之前先打个电话
Mm, just... try and call first.
好啦  我们说正事吧
Okay, let's get down to business.
华仔考虑投资一点钱
Howie was thinking about putting up some money
帮你重开漫画店
to help you reopen the store,
但在投资前  我有些问题要问
but before that happens, I have a few questions.
我很感谢你的慷慨解囊
I appreciate the offer,
但你妈妈已经给我钱了
but actually your mother already gave me the money.
什么
What?
是啊  我跟她说这太慷慨了
Yeah. I told her it was too much,
但她说能帮她的小乖乖她很开心
but she said she was happy to help out her bubala.
失陪下
Excuse me.
妈  你赶紧取消支票
Ma, you are canceling that check,
斯图尔特不是你的小乖乖  我才是
and Stuart is not your bubala; I'm your bubala.
你怎能同时拥有两个小乖乖呢
You can't have more than one bubala!
我不知道他在冲谁嚷嚷
I don't know who he's talking to.
他妈妈去百货店帮我买T恤了
She's at Target, buying me shirts.
我真开心问题解决了
I'm so glad we could work this all out.
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
你和莱纳德改天晚上和我们一起吃饭吧
You know, we should have dinner one night with you and Leonard.
我们太乐意了
Oh, we would love that.
太棒了
Great!
-晚安了  两位  -好的  晚安
- Okay, good night, guys. - All right, night.
拜
Bye.
-我讨厌她  -我讨厌她
- I hate her. - I hate her.
我真的很失望  我们不能开一家
I'm really disappointed we're not gonna have
-自己的漫画书店  -是啊
- our own comic book store. - I know.
我本来满心期待
I was looking forward to it.
能开一家自己的漫画书店多好啊
It would've been so nice to have a place that was ours,
我们可以安静地坐着在里面看漫画书
where we could just sit and read comics in peace.
有舒服的座位
With comfy seats.
还有零食
And snacks.
唉  哪有这么好的事啊
Well, I guess it was too good to be true.
没错
Yeah.